{
    "title": "JavaScript",

    "q": {
        "1": {
            "question": "How many keywords can declare variables in JavaScript ?",
            "choices": [
                "4 keywords",
                "3 keywords",
                "7 keywords"
            ],
            "answer": "3 keywords",
            "points": 1
        },
        "2": {
            "question": "JavaScript's varibales are____typing .",
            "choices": [
                "Static",
                "Script",
                "Dynamic"
            ],
            "answer": "Dynamic",
            "points": 2
        },
        "3": {
            "question": "JavaScript is scripting language, true or false?",
            "choices": [
                "true",
                "false",
                null
            ],
            "answer": "true",
            "points": 1
        },
        "4": {
            "question": "Which of the following is low level language ?",
            "choices": [
                "Laravel",
                "Jvascript",
                "Rust"
            ],
            "answer": "Rust",
            "points": 1
        },
        "5": {
            "question": "JavaScript code is a synchorounos. true or false?",
            "choices": [
                "true",
                "false",
                null
            ],
            "answer": "false",
            "points": 2
        },
        "6": {
            "question": "What the meaning of full-stack developer ?",
            "choices": [
                "Who is niether good in front-end or back-end",
                "Front-end and back-end developer",
                "Who is not good in front-end"
            ],
            "answer": "Front-end and back-end developer",
            "points": 3
        },
        "7": {
            "question": "JavaScript is used to develope____",
            "choices": [
                "Web / Mobile Apps",
                "Games / Real-time networking apps",
                "It's all true"
            ],
            "answer": "It's all true",
            "points": 3
        },
        "8": {
            "question": "The name of JavaScript Engine in firefox is____",
            "choices": [
                "SpiderMonkey",
                "ECMScript",
                "V8"
            ],
            "answer": "SpiderMonkey",
            "points": 3
        },
        "9": {
            "question": "To print values in JavaScript, you use____",
            "choices": [
                "console.echo()",
                "console.print()",
                "console.log()"
            ],
            "answer": "console.log()",
            "points": 2
        },
        "10": {
            "question": "Laravel is a framework for Jvascript. true or false?",
            "choices": [
                "true",
                "false",
                null
            ],
            "answer": "false",
            "points": 1
        },
        "11": {
            "question": "What is the output of console.log(10 + 2 + '20' + 3)?",
            "choices": [
                "102203",
                "12203",
                "25"
            ],
            "answer": "12203",
            "points": 1
        },
        "12": {
            "question": "Which method can be used to convert JavaScript object to JSON data?",
            "choices": [
                "json()",
                "stringify()",
                "parse()"
            ],
            "answer": "stringify()",
            "points": 2
        },
        "13": {
            "question": "What will console.log(typeof null) output?",
            "choices": [
                "null",
                "undefined",
                "object"
            ],
            "answer": "object",
            "points": 1.5
        },
        "14": {
            "question": "Which operator is used to check both of value and type?",
            "choices": [
                "=type=",
                "==",
                "==="
            ],
            "answer": "===",
            "points": 1
        },
        "15": {
            "question": "If num = 2 , the output of console.log(num==='2') will be____",
            "choices": [
                "2",
                "false",
                "true"
            ],
            "answer": "false",
            "points": 1.5
        },
        "16": {
            "question": "Which tag used to embed JavaScript?",
            "choices": [
                "<script>",
                "<code>",
                "<JavaScript>"
            ],
            "answer": "<script>",
            "points": 1
        },
        "17": {
            "question": "What is the output of console.log('4' * 3 + '5')?",
            "choices": [
                "125",
                "17",
                "4445"
            ],
            "answer": "125",
            "points": 2
        },
        "18": {
            "question": "How can you stop the execution of a setInterval() timer?",
            "choices": [
                "by using break;",
                "by using setInterval.clear()",
                "by using clearInterval()"
            ],
            "answer": "by using clearInterval()",
            "points": 2
        },
        "19": {
            "question": "What the value of new Set( [1, 2, 1, 3, 4, '2', 5] )?",
            "choices": [
                "1, 2, 3, 4, '2', 5",
                "[1, 2, 3, 4, 5]",
                "{1, 2, 3, 4, '2', 5}"
            ],
            "answer": "{1, 2, 3, 4, '2', 5}",
            "points": 3
        },
        "20": {
            "question": "What the output of console.log(!!'false')?",
            "choices": [
                "true",
                "false",
                "Throw an error"
            ],
            "answer": "true",
            "points": 3
        },
        "21": {
            "question": "What is the syntax of the ternary operator in JavaScript?",
            "choices": [
                "Condition ? a : b",
                "Condition : a : b",
                "Condition => a || b"
            ],
            "answer": "Condition ? a : b",
            "points": 3
        },
        "22": {
            "question": "JavaScript is used to make websites interactive, true or false?",
            "choices": [
                "true",
                "false",
                null
            ],
            "answer": "true",
            "points": 0.5
        },
        "23": {
            "question": "JavaScript is case-sensitive language, true or false?",
            "choices": [
                "true",
                "false",
                null
            ],
            "answer": "true",
            "points": 1
        },
        "24": {
            "question": "JavaScript is prototyped-based, true or false?",
            "choices": [
                "true",
                "false",
                null
            ],
            "answer": "true",
            "points": 1
        },
        "25": {
            "question": "When is better to use switch than use if-else?",
            "choices": [
                "When you want to check the condition on several cases",
                "When there are many if-else statements",
                "When you are not sure about the possible values of the condition"
            ],
            "answer": "When there are many if-else statements",
            "points": 3
        },
        "26": {
            "question": "To loop through the properties of an object, you use____",
            "choices": [
                "for loop",
                "for/of loop",
                "for/in loop"
            ],
            "answer": "for/in loop",
            "points": 2
        },
        "27": {
            "question": "which of the following are loops in JavaScript?",
            "choices": [
                "for, while, if/else",
                "while, for/of, for/in",
                "It's all false"
            ],
            "answer": "while, for/of, for/in",
            "points": 2
        },
        "28": {
            "question": "To loop through the values of an array, you use____",
            "choices": [
                "for loop",
                "for/of loop",
                "for/in loop"
            ],
            "answer": "for/of loop",
            "points": 2
        },
        "29": {
            "question": "What method is used to compute the milliseconds from 1970/1/1 00:00:00 til today?",
            "choices": [
                "getDate()",
                "getMilliseconds()",
                "getTime()"
            ],
            "answer": "getTime()",
            "points": 3
        },
        "30": {
            "question": "The method which used to check if the first of the string is a specific charachter?",
            "choices": [
                "firstChar()",
                "charAt()",
                "startsWith()"
            ],
            "answer": "startsWith()",
            "points": 3
        },
        "31": {
            "question": "What the output of console.log( 'JavaScript'.slice(1,-1) )?",
            "choices": [
                "avaScriptJ",
                "avaScrip",
                "Throw an error"
            ],
            "answer": "avaScrip",
            "points": 3
        },
        "32": {
            "question": "What the last index of an array which has length = 4?",
            "choices": [
                "3",
                "4",
                "5"
            ],
            "answer": "3",
            "points": 1
        },
        "33": {
            "question": "The method indexOf() is used with____",
            "choices": [
                "strings",
                "arrays",
                "both"
            ],
            "answer": "both",
            "points": 1
        },
        "34": {
            "question": "What the meaning of the method chaining in JavaScript?",
            "choices": [
                "Calling a method sevral times",
                "Calling a method after another",
                "Calling a method after another in on continous line"
            ],
            "answer": "Calling a method after another in on continous line",
            "points": 2
        },
        "35": {
            "question": "What the logical operator of OR in JavaScript?",
            "choices": [
                "OR",
                "||",
                "!&"
            ],
            "answer": "||",
            "points": 1
        },
        "36": {
            "question": "The syntax of for loop is____",
            "choices": [
                "for(initial: limit: increment){}",
                "for(initial; limit; increment) => {}",
                "for(initial; limit; increment){}"
            ],
            "answer": "for(initial; limit; increment){}",
            "points": 3
        },
        "37": {
            "question": "What the method that used to delete the first element in an array?",
            "choices": [
                "shift()",
                "unshift()",
                "pop()"
            ],
            "answer": "shift()",
            "points": 3
        },
        "38": {
            "question": "What the method that used to add an element to the last of an array?",
            "choices": [
                "push()",
                "add()",
                "insert()"
            ],
            "answer": "push()",
            "points": 2
        },
        "39": {
            "question": "What the use of rest parameters",
            "choices": [
                "Expand an array into seperate elements",
                "Bundles seperate elements into an array",
                "It's all false"
            ],
            "answer": "Bundles seperate elements into an array",
            "points": 3
        },
        "40": {
            "question": "A function that is passed as an argument to another function",
            "choices": [
                "Callback",
                "Callback hell",
                "Recursion"
            ],
            "answer": "CallBack",
            "points": 2
        },
        "41": {
            "question": "The difference between map() and forEach()",
            "choices": [
                "forEach() returns a new array",
                "map() returns a new array",
                "map() is used with objects"
            ],
            "answer": "map() returns a new array",
            "points": 3
        },
        "42": {
            "question": "How to sum the values of an array ?",
            "choices": [
                "Using reduce() method",
                "Using fisher-yates algorithm",
                "Using for/of loop"
            ],
            "answer": "Using reduce() method",
            "points": 3
        },
        "43": {
            "question": "How to shuffle the elements of an array ?",
            "choices": [
                "Using sort() method",
                "Using fisher-yates algorithm",
                "Using for/of loop"
            ],
            "answer": "Using fisher-yates algorithm",
            "points": 3
        },
        "44": {
            "question": "How to swap between values of variables?",
            "choices": [
                "[a , b] = [b , a]",
                "a, b = b, a",
                "a = b & b = a"
            ],
            "answer": "[a , b] = [b , a]",
            "points": 2
        },
        "45": {
            "question": "'this' keyword is refrence to the____",
            "choices": [
                "array where 'this' used",
                "function where 'this' used",
                "object where 'this' used"
            ],
            "answer": "object where 'this' used",
            "points": 1
        },
        "46": {
            "question": "super keyword is refrence to the____",
            "choices": [
                "first object",
                "parent of the object",
                "child of the object"
            ],
            "answer": "parent of the object",
            "points": 1
        },
        "47": {
            "question": "sort((a, b) => a.localeCompare(b)) is used to____",
            "choices": [
                "sort an array of string ascading",
                "sort an array of string descadng",
                "sort an array of numbers ascading"
            ],
            "answer": "sort an array of string ascading",
            "points": 3
        },
        "48": {
            "question": "Which method used to get the year of a date",
            "choices": [
                "getYear()",
                "getFullYear()",
                "getYearOfDate()"
            ],
            "answer": "getFullYear()",
            "points": 2
        },
        "49": {
            "question": "Which of the following is used to replay a code block after specific time",
            "choices": [
                "setTimer()",
                "setInterval()",
                "setTimeout()"
            ],
            "answer": "setInterval()",
            "points": 2
        },
        "50": {
            "question": "Errors can be handled with____blocks",
            "choices": [
                "async/await/then",
                "switch/case/default",
                "try/catch/finally"
            ],
            "answer": "try/catch/finally",
            "points": 3
        },
        "51": {
            "question": "____is a function-scoped",
            "choices": [
                "let",
                "var",
                "const"
            ],
            "answer": "var",
            "points": 2
        },
        "52": {
            "question": "Which of these is used to declare variables that won't be reassigned?",
            "choices": [
                "let",
                "var",
                "const"
            ],
            "answer": "const",
            "points": 3
        },
        "53": {
            "question": "How can you create a function in JavaScript?",
            "choices": [
                "function(){}",
                "const function = () => {}",
                "It's all true"
            ],
            "answer": "const function = () => {}",
            "points": 2
        },
        "54": {
            "question": "Arrow functions have their own 'this' value, true or false?",
            "choices": [
                "true",
                "false",
                null
            ],
            "answer": "false",
            "points": 1
        },
        "55": {
            "question": "How do you add event to a DOM element?",
            "choices": [
                "element.addEventListener('event-name', function())",
                "element.addEventListener('event-name', () => {})",
                "It's all false"
            ],
            "answer": "element.addEventListener('event-name', () => {})",
            "points": 3
        },
        "56": {
            "question": "The promise is representing the eventual completion, true or false?",
            "choices": [
                "true",
                "false",
                null
            ],
            "answer": "true",
            "points": 1
        }
    }
}